export const set1 = [
    // Finite or Infinite
    { numb: 1, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "4 + 3 =", options: ["5", "6", "7", "8"], answer: "7", tag: "Finite" },
    { numb: 2, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "6 + 5 =", options: ["10", "11", "12", "13"], answer: "11", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 3, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "8 + 4 =", options: ["11", "12", "13", "14"], answer: "12", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 4, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "6 + 9 =", options: ["14", "15", "16", "17"], answer: "15", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 5, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "7 + 9 =", options: ["15", "16", "17", "18"], answer: "16", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 6, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "9 + 8 =", options: ["16", "17", "18", "19"], answer: "17", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 7, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "9 + 9 =", options: ["17", "18", "19", "20"], answer: "18", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 8, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "4 + 3 =", options: ["5", "6", "7", "8"], answer: "7", tag: "Finite" },
    { numb: 9, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "6 + 2 =", options: ["7", "8", "9", "10"], answer: "8", tag: "Finite" },
    { numb: 10, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "4 + 9 =", options: ["12", "13", "14", "15"], answer: "13", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 11, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "7 + 6 =", options: ["12", "13", "14", "15"], answer: "13", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 12, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "8 + 4 =", options: ["11", "12", "13", "14"], answer: "12", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 13, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "6 + 9 =", options: ["14", "15", "16", "17"], answer: "15", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 14, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "5 + 8 =", options: ["12", "13", "14", "15"], answer: "13", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 15, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "4 + 9 =", options: ["12", "13", "14", "15"], answer: "13", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 16, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "9 + 8 =", options: ["16", "17", "18", "19"], answer: "17", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 17, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "3 + 6 =", options: ["8", "9", "10", "11"], answer: "9", tag: "Finite" },
    { numb: 18, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "7 + 8 =", options: ["14", "15", "16", "17"], answer: "15", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 19, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "8 + 8 =", options: ["15", "16", "17", "18"], answer: "16", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 20, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "5 + 7 =", options: ["11", "12", "13", "14"], answer: "12", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 21, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "2 + 5 =", options: ["6", "7", "8", "9"], answer: "7", tag: "Finite" },
    { numb: 22, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "7 + 9 =", options: ["15", "16", "17", "18"], answer: "16", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 23, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "8 + 6 =", options: ["13", "14", "15", "16"], answer: "14", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 24, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "5 + 3 =", options: ["7", "8", "9", "10"], answer: "8", tag: "Finite" },
    { numb: 25, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "7 + 9 =", options: ["15", "16", "17", "18"], answer: "16", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 26, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "6 + 5 =", options: ["10", "11", "12", "13"], answer: "11", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 27, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "8 + 7 =", options: ["14", "15", "16", "17"], answer: "15", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 28, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "8 + 4 =", options: ["11", "12", "13", "14"], answer: "12", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 29, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "8 + 5 =", options: ["12", "13", "14", "15"], answer: "13", tag: "Infinite" },
    { numb: 30, type: "Finite or Infinite", question: "9 + 9 =", options: ["17", "18", "19", "20"], answer: "18", tag: "Infinite" },

    // END Number
    { numb: 31, type: "END Number", question: "9 + 7 =", options: ["15", "16", "17", "18"], answer: "16", end: "6" },
    { numb: 32, type: "END Number", question: "5 + 6 =", options: ["10", "11", "12", "13"], answer: "11", end: "1" },
    { numb: 33, type: "END Number", question: "4 + 8 =", options: ["12", "13", "14", "15"], answer: "12", end: "2" },
    { numb: 34, type: "END Number", question: "5 + 8 =", options: ["10", "11", "12", "13"], answer: "13", end: "3" },
    { numb: 35, type: "END Number", question: "7 + 7 =", options: ["13", "14", "15", "16"], answer: "14", end: "4" },
    { numb: 36, type: "END Number", question: "8 + 8 =", options: ["15", "16", "17", "18"], answer: "16", end: "6" },
    { numb: 37, type: "END Number", question: "7 + 8 =", options: ["14", "15", "16", "17"], answer: "15", end: "5" },
    { numb: 38, type: "END Number", question: "9 + 4 =", options: ["12", "13", "14", "15"], answer: "13", end: "3" },
    { numb: 39, type: "END Number", question: "7 + 6 =", options: ["12", "13", "14", "15"], answer: "13", end: "3" },
    { numb: 40, type: "END Number", question: "6 + 9 =", options: ["14", "15", "16", "17"], answer: "15", end: "5" }
];
